sanatansociety.org 2011-06-30

# Sanatan Society Privacy Statement

**SANATAN SOCIETY Privacy Statement**  

This document was last updated November 17, 2002. 

SANATAN SOCIETY is committed to protecting your privacy. You can visit most pages on our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, and this privacy statement explains data collection and use in those situations. 

**Collection of your Personal Information**

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are registering before asking for information, ordering e-mail newsletters or when purchasing SANATAN SOCIETY products. Personal information collected by SANATAN SOCIETY.com often is limited to e-mail address, language, country or location, but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested.

For example: If you choose a service or transaction that requires payment, such as making a purchase in the Shop area of the Web site, we will request personal information necessary for billing and/or shipping, such as: name, address, telephone number, and credit card number.

When you buy and install a new product, we may ask you to register your purchase electronically. We keep this registration information on file with any information you've already given us on previous visits to our Web site.

SANATAN SOCIETY.com also collects certain information about your computer hardware and software. This information may include: your IP address, browser type, operating system, domain name, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of SANATAN SOCIETY.com.

SANATAN SOCIETY.com also collects information about which pages our customers visit within SANATAN SOCIETY.com. This site visitation data is identified only by a unique ID number, and it is never linked with personal information unless a user consents as described below.

**Use of your Personal Information**

We will merge site-visitation data with anonymous demographic information for research purposes, and we may use this information in aggregate to provide more relevant content.

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging, mailing and delivering purchases, sending postal mail and processing event registration. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

SANATAN SOCIETY may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on SANATAN SOCIETY or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of SANATAN SOCIETY and its family of Web sites, or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of SANATAN SOCIETY employees, users of SANATAN SOCIETY products or services, or members of the public.

**Control of your Personal Information**

When you register, or otherwise give us personal information, SANATAN SOCIETY.com will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above.

SANATAN SOCIETY.com does not allow other companies to offer our registered customers information about their products and services.

**Security of your Personal Information**

SANATAN SOCIETY.com is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When we transmit sensitive information (such as a credit card number) over the internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Use of Cookies**

We do not use cookies on our Sites.

**Changes to this Statement**

SANATAN SOCIETY.com will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this statement, SANATAN SOCIETY.com will notify you by placing prominent notice on the Web site.
